At school you're surrounded by people your own age.
在学校，你身边都是同龄人。
Of course you spend a lot of time with them, and so some of the best friendships are forged at school.
你当然会花很多时间与他们相处，因此一些最牢固的友谊就是在学校建立的。
But later in life, it's easy to lose touch – you work full-time, maybe start a family, and your old friends might be scattered across the country or even the world.
但在以后的生活中，很容易失去联系——你全职工作，也许组建了家庭，而你的老朋友可能分散在全国甚至世界各地。
A 2016 study in Finland found that after the age of 25, the number of friends someone has falls very quickly, and this number continues to decrease throughout a person's life.
芬兰2016年的一项研究发现，25岁以后，一个人的朋友数量会迅速下降，而且这个数字会在一生中持续减少。
So when you're in your mid-to-late 20s, how can you make new friends?
那么，当你处于二十多岁中后期时，如何才能结交新朋友呢？
Radhika Sanghani, a BBC journalist, tasked herself with making new friends by saying 'yes' to any invitations that came her way.
BBC记者拉迪卡·桑哈尼给自己定下任务，对任何找上门的邀请都说"好"，以此结交新朋友。
If a colleague asked her for lunch, she didn't shy away from it, and she soon made some of the closest friends she'd ever had.
如果有同事约她吃午饭，她不会回避，很快她就交到了一些她有史以来最亲密的朋友。"
"We all message several times a week often leaving rambling voice notes; we host dinners at each other's houses; and we've all cried on each other at least once (the true mark of friendship)" she wrote in a 2018 article.
我们每周都会发几次消息，经常留下冗长的语音留言；我们在彼此家里举办晚餐聚会；而且我们至少都在对方面前哭过一次（友谊的真正标志），"她在2018年的一篇文章中写道。
The website Talk Twenties recommends joining a local class or group, like taking up running or joining a choir.
网站"二十多岁交谈"建议加入当地的课程或团体，比如开始跑步或加入合唱团。
Having something in common gives you something to talk about with your new acquaintances, which will hopefully then translate into meaningful relationships.
拥有共同点能让你与新认识的人有话题可聊，这有望随后转化为有意义的关系。
When you don't have mutual interests with someone, it can be difficult to get past the small talk stage, where conversation can quickly fizzle out, and a class can help avoid this.
当你与他人没有共同兴趣时，很难度过闲聊阶段，在这个阶段对话可能很快无疾而终，而参加课程有助于避免这种情况。
Nowadays, there are also apps for meeting new people, like Bumble BFF or Meetup.
如今，也有用于结识新朋友的应用程序，比如Bumble BFF或Meetup。
Dr Robert Puff who writes for Psychology Today says solid friendships are essential for two main reasons.
为《今日心理学》撰稿的罗伯特·帕夫博士说，牢固的友谊至关重要，主要有两个原因。
One is to help make life more enjoyable, and two is for support in difficult times – to make hardships more tolerable!
一是帮助让生活更愉快，二是在困难时期提供支持——让艰难时刻更易于忍受！
As we grow up, we can feel like we're not in control of what's happening around us, but we can control our social life, so enrich your life with fulfilling friendships.
随着我们长大，我们可能会觉得自己无法控制周围发生的事情，但我们可以控制自己的社交生活，所以要用令人满意的友谊来丰富你的生活。